Y'all be knowing that you don't know nothing about history and you will still come on with your
enraging. Like it makes me furious. Comparing a politician, all caps, to activists is why this
conversation seems to keep cycling over and over even after the election. I don't think anyone
thinks Kamala is an activist. So expect radical activism is kind of a setup for disappointment.
It's like expecting a warden to burn down the prison or insert any other system institution
instead. The expectation at best can only be to treat the prisoners fairly. The deep irony
of comparing a DA, a former DA to a warden in a prison is, is I don't even have the time.
Okay. But let's unpack this. I need y'all to understand that black people being in politics
was activism because we weren't allowed in it. Do you understand that? We weren't in this reality.
Okay. And Wilcox was so mad about black politics after reconstruction that they came and then held
everybody who was in position up. They held them up and said, nah, we're in charge now.
After the civil rights movement of the sixties, black people were given access to now be a part
of electoral government. And in that access, it was activism to come into those positions by nature of
the fact that you were now activating the action you had been doing the activism for.
And then they tricked you. They tricked you into thinking now that you're in here, that's it.
You did it. The goal was to get in, not to change it from within. And then they undermined every
political movement that was happening outside so that there couldn't be any coalition building
with the folks on the outside doing the work and the folks now inside doing the work. And y'all sit
up here on this app every single day and you co-sign it. You co-sign COINTELPRO. You co-sign the
murder of Fred Hampton and you don't even realize it. And you say things like comparing a politician
to activists when it's applying to a black person who is aligning herself and making her identity and
her politics all about being black. And you think you're saying something and all you're saying is
that they defeated you. You damn rude, eh?